Council on Foreign Relations Records: Studies Department Series, 1918-2004: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Subseries 3B: Records of Groups, 1918-1996; 91.12 linear feet 219 boxes
  - Projects, 1918-1999; 49 boxes (1 partial)
    - 1980s Project (First Meeting, 1974 May 2), 18 boxes (2 partial)
      - Authors, 1973-1979; 3 boxes (2 partial)
        - Lewis, John A. Miscellaneous Paper, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 19)
        - Lockwood, Bert on Transinternational Violence and Subversion, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 20)
        - McCulloch, Rachel on International Trade, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 21)
        - Makins, Christopher on Transinternational Violence and Subversion, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 22)
        - Mandelbaum, Michael on Nuclear Weapons, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 23)
        - Oppenheimer, Michael Miscellaneous Paper, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 24)
        - Pauker, Guy on North-South Relations, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 25)
        - Pelkmans, Jacques on Macroeconomic Policies and International Monetary Relations, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 26)
        - Pinera, Jose on International Trade, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 27)
        - Rodley, Nigel on Human Rights, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 28)
        - Rodriguez, Carlos on Macroeconomic Policies and International Monetary Relations, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 29)
        - Taylor, Theodore on Nuclear Weapons, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 30)
        - Vogel, David on International Investment and Multinational Corporation, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 31)
        - Waterbury, John on North-South Relations, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 1)
        - Whitaker, Ben on Human Rights, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 2)
        - Wiggins, Howard on North-South Relations, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 3)
        - Zartman, I. William on North-South Relations, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 4)
      - Authors-Incomplete Papers, 1975-1979; 2 folders
        - Bryant-Nerlich, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 5)
        - Ng'weno-Rackzowski, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 6)
      - Violence and Subversion Group, 1975-1976; 7 folders
        - Focus and Mandate, 1975; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 7)
        - Membership and Invites, 1976; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 8)
        - "Note on Treatment of Violence...", 1975; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 9)
        - Planning and Organization Miscellaneous, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 10)
        - Deutch Comments on Meetings and Papers, 1976; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 11)
        - First Meeting, 1976 March 27; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 12)
        - Second Meeting, 1976 May 6; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 13)
      - Human Rights Group, 1975-1976; 9 folders
        - General Correspondence and Memos, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 14)
        - Hesburgh, Theodore (Chairman), 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 15)
        - Membership and Invitations, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 16)
        - Mandate and Focus, 1975; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 17)
        - Planning and Organization, 1976; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 18)
        - First Meeting, 1975 December 10; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 19)
        - Second Meeting, 1976 March 2; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 20)
        - Third Meeting, 1976 March 18; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 21)
        - Fourth Meeting, 1976 April 22; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 22)
      - North-South Relations Group, 1975-1976; 9 folders
        - Mandate and Focus, 1975; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 23)
        - Nye Jr., Joseph S. (Chairman), 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 24)
        - Planning and Organization, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 25)
        - Membership and Invitations, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 26)
        - Gompert Memo on Proliferation and South Goals, 1976; 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 27)
        - Meetings, 1976 April 7-June 18; 4 folders
          - 1976 April 7, 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 28)
          - 1976 April 23, 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 29)
          - 1976 May 20, 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 30)
          - 1976 June 18, 1 folder (Box 308, Folder 31)
      - Environmental/Global Commons/Economic Growth Group, 1975-1977; 12 folders
        - Focus and Mandate, 1975; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 1)
        - Skolnikoff, Eugene (Chairman), 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 2)
        - Planning and Organization, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 3)
        - Hopkins Paper-Evaluations, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 4)
        - Membership and Invitations, 1976; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence with Participants, 1976; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 6)
        - Comments on Paper and Meetings, 1976; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 7)
        - Meetings, 1976 March 4-June 2; 4 folders
          - 1976 March 4, 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 8)
          - 1976 May 12, 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 9)
          - 1976 May 13, 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 10)
          - 1976 June 2, 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 11)
        - Hollick, Ann, "Oceans Regime" draft, 1976; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 12)
      - Ullman, Richard, Chapters, 1979; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 13)
      - International Trade Group, 1975-1976; 7 folders
        - Memberships and Invitations, 1975-1976; portion of 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 14)
        - Correspondence, 1975-1976; portion of 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 15)
        - Mandate and Focus, 1975; portion of 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 14)
        - McQuade, Lawrence (Chairman), 1976; portion of 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 15)
        - Planning and Organization, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 16)
        - Meetings, 1976 February 10-June 21; 4 folders
          - 1976 February 10, 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 17)
          - 1976 March 23, 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 18)
          - 1976 April 20, 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 19)
          - 1976 June 21, 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 20)
      - Industrial Policy Group, 1974-1989; portions of 2 boxes
        - Focus and Mandate, 1975; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 21)
        - Members and Invitations, 1976; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 22)
        - Correspondence and Memos, Miscellaneous, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 23)
        - Meetings 1, 2 and 3, 1976; 1 folder (Box 309, Folder 24)
        - Diebold, William, 1974-1989; 2 folders
          - "Industrial Policy as an International Issue in the 1980s and Beyond," 1976, 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 1)
          - Memos, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 2)
      - International Investment and the Multinational Corporations Group, 1975-1976; 6 folders
        - Focus and Mandate, 1975; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 3)
        - Planning and Organization, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 4)
        - Memberships and Invitations, 1976; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 5)
        - Questionnaire, 1976; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 6)
        - Meetings, 1976 June 4-September 14; 2 folders
          - 1976 June 4, 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 7)
          - 1976 September 14, 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 8)
      - Macroeconomic Policies and International Monetary Relations Group, 1975-1976; 9 folders
        - Focus, 1975; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 9)
        - Cleveland, Harold Van B. (Chairman), 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 10)
        - Memberships and Invitations, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 11)
        - Correspondence, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 12)
        - Meetings, 1975 December 9-1976 June 9; 5 folders
          - 1975 December 9, 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 13)
          - 1976 February 5, 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 14)
          - 1976 April 21, 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 15)
          - 1976 May 21, 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 16)
          - 1976 June 9, 1 folder (Box 310, Folder 17)
      - Armed Conflict Group, 1975-1977 March 21; 10 folders
        - Focus and Mandate, 1975; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 1)
        - Gelb, Leslie (Chairman), 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 2)
        - Membership and Invitations, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 3)
        - Planning and Organization, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 4)
        - Meetings, 1976 February 24-1977 March 21; 6 folders
          - 1976 February 24, 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 5)
          - 1976 March 2, 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 6)
          - 1976 March 17, 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 7)
          - 1976 April 15, 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 8)
          - 1976 May 4, 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 9)
          - 1977 March 21, 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 10)
      - Nuclear Weapons Group, 1975-1977; 11 folders
        - Focus and Mandate, 1975; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 11)
        - Membership and Invitations, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 12)
        - Planning and Organization, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 13)
        - Vance, Cyrus (Chairman), 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 14)
        - Sharfman, Peter, Comments, 1975; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 15)
        - Meetings, 1975 November 19-1976 May 3; 6 folders
          - 1975 November 19, 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 16)
          - 1976 January 14, 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 17)
          - 1976 February 4, 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 18)
          - 1976 March 10, 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 19)
          - 1976 April 8, 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 20)
          - 1976 May 3, 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 21)
      - Project Coordination Group, 1974-1977; portions of 2 boxes
        - Planning and Organization and Membership, 1974-1977; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 22)
        - Correspondence with Members, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 311, Folder 23)
        - Meeting, 1975 March 21-1976 June 7; 6 folders
          - 1975 March 21-22, 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 1)
          - 1975 May 9-10, 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 2)
          - 1975 June 27-28, 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 3)
          - 1975 December 17, 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 4)
          - 1976 February 18, 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 5)
          - 1976 June 7, 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 6)
      - Conferences, 1974-1979; 5 folders
        - Seven Springs Planning Conference, 1974; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 7)
        - Moscow (June 1977), 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 8)
        - Industrial Policy, Bellagio (March 1978), 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 9)
        - Industrial Policy, Bellagio (March 1978), 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 10)
        - Seven Springs (May 1979), 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 312, Folder 11)
      - Approaches to Focus Group Issues, 1975-1976; 2 folders
        - "Autonomy and Identity"-"Peacekeeping and Pacific Settlement", 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 1)
        - "Population and Growth"-"Welfare", 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 2)
      - Independent Study, 1975-1979; 15 folders
        - Azrael, Jeremy, "Protests and Rights in USSRll, LZ", 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 3)
        - Caldwell, Lawrence T., "Soviet-American Relations in the 1980s", 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 4)
        - Dernberger, Robert F., "China's Economic Evolution and it's Implications", 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 5)
        - Falk, Richard, "Responding to Severe Violations", 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 6)
        - Green, Donald, Levine, Herbert and Miovic, Peter, "Soviet Economy in the 1980s", 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 7)
        - Hasner, Pierre, "Change in European Politics", 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 8)
        - Huntzinger, Jacques, "Arms Importer Restraint", 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 9)
        - Langdon, Steven and Mytelka, Lynn, "Africa in Economy", 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 10)
        - Levine, Herbert on the Soviet Union, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 11)
        - Mates, Leo, "US in the 1980s", 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 12)
        - Noreng, Øystein on International Energy Corporation, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 13)
        - Piotrow, Phyllis, "Population Policies for the 1980s", 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 14)
        - Whiting, Allen, China and the 1980s, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 15)
        - Williamson, John on International Borrowing, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 16)
        - Wood, Bryce, "Human Rights in Latin America", 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 313, Folder 17)
      - International Institutions Group, General, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 1)
      - Distribution of Income Group, General, 1975; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 2)
      - Articles and Reviews of the Project, 1978; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 3)
      - General Papers Commissioned, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 4)
      - Publication, 1975-1979; portions of 2 boxes
        - General, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 5)
        - McGraw-Hill Correspondence, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 6)
        - Front Matter for Books, 1976; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 7)
        - Press Release, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 8)
        - Publicity Lists, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence, re: Reviews, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 314, Folder 10)
        - Advertising, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 1)
        - Free Copies, 1977; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 2)
        - Advertising-World Without War, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 3)
        - McGraw Hill Miscellaneous-Contract info, Discount Agreements, Reprints, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 4)
        - Sales Figures, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 5)
      - Frame Working Essays, 1976-1977; 2 folders
        - "Alternatives to Monetary Disorder"-"International Disaster Relief", 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 6)
        - "Middle East"-"Soviet-American", 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 7)
      - Reviews, 1976-1981; portions of 2 boxes
        - "Africa in the 1980s", 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 8)
        - "Alternatives to Monetary Disorder", 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 9)
        - "Beyond the North-South Stalemate", 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 10)
        - "Challenges to Interdependent Economies", 1978; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 11)
        - "China's Future", 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 12)
        - "Collective Management", 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 13)
        - "Controlling Future Arms Trade", 1977; 1979; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 14)
        - "Diversity and Development in South East Asia", 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 15)
        - "Enhancing Global Human Rights", 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 16)
        - "Growth Policies and the International Order", 1978; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 17)
        - "Industrial Policy", 1978-1981; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 18)
        - "International Disaster Relief", 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 19)
        - "Middle East in the Coming Decade", 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 315, Folder 20)
        - "Nuclear Proliferation", 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 1)
        - "Nuclear Weapons and World Politics", 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 2)
        - "Oil Politics", 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 3)
        - "Reducing Global Inequities", 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 4)
        - "Rich and Poor Nations", 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 5)
        - "Sharing Global Resources", 1978; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 6)
        - "Six Billion People", 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 7)
        - "Soviet-American Relations", 1979; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 8)
      - Inreach, 1974-1979; 7 folders
        - General, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 9)
        - Publication Notices, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 10)
        - Meetings for Council Membership, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 11)
        - Committee on Foreign Relations, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 12)
        - Correspondence re: Paper Distribution, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 13)
        - Individual Members, Altschul-Thomas, 1974-1977; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 14)
        - Ullman, Richard, Memo, 1976 July; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 15)
      - Outreach, 1975-1979; 3 boxes (2 partial)
        - American Political Science Association Meetings, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 16)
        - Arms Transfer Conference, 1978 February 25; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 17)
        - Articles re: Project, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 316, Folder 18)
        - Association of American Publishers Dinner, 1977 October 17; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 1)
        - Bergen Community College TV Series, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 2)
        - Budget/Finances, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 3)
        - Books to Eastern Europe, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 4)
        - Editorial Briefing, 1976 December 13; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 5)
        - Garwin/Mandelbaum NPR Program, 1977 November 9; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 6)
        - General, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 7)
        - Government Relations, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 8)
        - Hansch, Roger Meeting, 1978 August 31; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 9)
        - International Studies Association, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 10)
        - Library Exchanges, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 11)
        - Newsletter, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 12)
        - Oregon Pilot Policy Project, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 13)
        - Organizations, Aspen-United Nations, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 14)
        - Overseas Development Council Agreement re: Hansen Book, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 15)
        - Press Conference, 1977 April 12; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 16)
        - Radio, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 17)
        - Requests from Individuals Adams-Zeman, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 317, Folder 18)
        - Requests from Institutions, American Bar Association-World Peace Foundation, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 1)
        - Requests for Information from International Governments,1976-1979, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 2)
        - Requests from Libraries, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 3)
        - Requests from Universities, AACSB-Yeshiva, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 4)
        - Reviewer's Lunch, 1977 November 15; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 5)
        - Television, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 6)
        - Trade Conventions, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 7)
        - World Affairs Councils, Buffalo-Vermont, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 8)
      - Diebold, William, 1974-1976; 2 folders
        - Correspondence-General (Possible Duplicates), 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence-General (Possible Duplicates), 1976; 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 10)
    - Latin America Project (First Meeting, 1975 February 4), portions of 2 boxes
      - 1973-1975, 1982-1984, 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 11)
      - 1985-1987, 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 12)
      - 1986-1991, 1 folder (Box 318, Folder 13)
      - 1987-1988, 1990, 1 folder (Box 319, Folder 1)
      - 1991-1994, 1 folder (Box 319, Folder 2)
    - Canada Project (First Meeting, 1977 November 10), portions of 2 boxes
      - 1972, 1978-1979, 1 folder (Box 319, Folder 3)
      - 1980-1982, 1 folder (Box 319, Folder 4)
      - 1982-1983, 1 folder (Box 319, Folder 5)
      - 1984, 1 folder (Box 320, Folder 1)
      - 1984-1986, 1 folder (Box 320, Folder 2)
      - 1986-1990, 1 folder (Box 320, Folder 3)
    - Soviet Project (First Meeting, 1978 November 8), portions of 2 boxes
      - 1978-1984, 2 folders (Box 320, Folder 4 to 5)
      - 1985-1987, 1 folder (Box 320, Folder 6)
      - 1987-1990, 1 folder (Box 320, Folder 7)
      - Détente Papers, 1978; 1983; 1 folder (Box 321, Folder 1)
      - Soviet Exchange with CFR, 1988-1989; 1 folder (Box 321, Folder 2)
    - Africa Project (First Meeting, 1978), 1976-1984; portions of 2 boxes
      - Correspondence (Manuscripts), 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 321, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence (Manuscripts), 1979-1983; 1 folder (Box 321, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence and Reports, 1977-1982; 1 folder (Box 321, Folder 5)
      - Funding and Budget, 1978-1984; 1 folder (Box 321, Folder 6)
      - Opinion Survey, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 321, Folder 7)
      - Planning and Organization, 1976-1980; 1 folder (Box 321, Folder 8)
      - Wingspread Conference, 1979; 1 folder (Box 322, Folder 1)
    - European American Project (First Meeting, 1980 November 24), 8 boxes (1 partial)
      - Administrative, 1982-1990; 7 folders
        - Correspondence, 1984; 1987; 1 folder (Box 322, Folder 2)
        - Funding, General, 1982-1986; 1 folder (Box 322, Folder 3)
        - Funding, Ford Foundation, 1982-1990; 1 folder (Box 322, Folder 4)
        - Funding, German Marshall Fund, 1982-1987; 1 folder (Box 322, Folder 5)
        - Funding, Mellon Foundation, 1982-1989; 1 folder (Box 322, Folder 6)
        - Funding, Rockefeller Foundation, 1982-1988; 1 folder (Box 322, Folder 7)
        - Planning, 1982-1989; 1 folder (Box 322, Folder 8)
      - Nuclear, 1980-1993; 3 boxes (1 partial)
        - Press Release, Summary and Lord, Winston, Letter re: Western Security, 1981; 1 folder (Box 322, Folder 9)
        - Outside Correspondence, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 322, Folder 10)
        - Mailing Lists Distribution of Western Society, 1981; 1 folder (Box 323, Folder 1)
        - Materials re: Meetings, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 323, Folder 2)
        - "Western Security", 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 323, Folder 3)
        - Basic Documents, 1980-1981; more than 1 folder
          - 1980-1981, 2 folders (Box 323, Folder 4 to 5)
        - Studies, 1982-1983; 1 folder (Box 323, Folder 6)
        - Studies Administration, 1983-1993; more than 1 folder
          - 1983-1993, 2 folders (Box 323, Folder 7 to 8)
        - Background Articles for "Western Security", 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 324, Folder 1)
        - Comments on "Western Security", 1981; 1 folder (Box 324, Folder 2)
        - "Western Security" Press File, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 324, Folder 3)
        - "Western Security," Final Product in English and German, 1981; 1 folder (Box 324, Folder 4)
        - "Canada and Western Security", 1982; 1 folder (Box 324, Folder 5)
        - Nuclear Press Conference, 1984 January 30; 1 folder (Box 324, Folder 6)
        - Advisory Group Nuclear Meeting, 1983 June 9-September 12; 2 folders
          - 1983 September 12, 1 folder (Box 324, Folder 7)
          - 1983 June 9, 1 folder (Box 324, Folder 8)
        - Weapons Distributions, 1984; 1 folder (Box 324, Folder 9)
        - Correspondence, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 324, Folder 10)
        - Book Reviews, 1984; 1 folder (Box 324, Folder 11)
        - Digest, 1983 September 12; 1 folder (Box 324, Folder 12)
        - Outline for and Critiques of Nukes in Europe, 1983; 1 folder (Box 324, Folder 13)
      - Unemployment, 1983-1986; 17 folders
        - Advisory Group Meeting, 1983; 1 folder (Box 325, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence, 1984; 1 folder (Box 325, Folder 2)
        - Paris-London Press Conference, 1984; 1 folder (Box 325, Folder 3)
        - Advisory Group Meeting Notes, 1984; 1 folder (Box 325, Folder 4)
        - UNA Project on Unemployment, 1983; 1 folder (Box 325, Folder 5)
        - Distribution, 1984; 1 folder (Box 325, Folder 6)
        - Critiques of Manuscript, 1984; 1 folder (Box 325, Folder 7)
        - Outside Publishers, 1984-1986; 1 folder (Box 325, Folder 8)
        - Digest and Questions, 1983 September 26; 1 folder (Box 325, Folder 9)
        - Press Conference, 1984 May 10; 1 folder (Box 325, Folder 10)
        - Yale Book News on "The Making of America's Soviet Policy", 1984; 1 folder (Box 325, Folder 11)
        - Advisory Group Meeting, 1984 January 9; 1 folder (Box 325, Folder 12)